friends, in the last few decades, there has been
significant progress in medical technology, with the
help of which treatment of diseases was not possible earlier.
With the continuous advancement of technology, the
cost of treatment has also increased compared to earlier.
This is becoming a matter of concern for the middle class people.
Due to the cost of other expenses related to medical procedures, everyone
should know the opinion of experts
about some health insurance plans
and their benefits as well as to know
about the policy.
You all must have a good health policy.
Choosing one of those health policies is a
difficult task. Let us know what are the facilities provided in a good health
insurance policy and what are the security and facilities in a health policy.
This policy is designed to
ensure worry-free medical treatment.
This policy also gives the
flexibility to choose any room in the hospital. Along with this, there is an
option to appoint maternity and child benefits.
You can buy this policy by spending Rs. 5 per month. The
premium for this health insurance plan is
₹5000 per year. The insurance cover is ₹50000 per year. The expenses after the death of the member in the year of
encounter with security forces with the same period of the
first hospitalization.
It covers
- Expenses incurred on 140 procedures and treatments Hospitalization expenses
incurred at home
Hospitalization expenses before hospitalization Post hospitalization expenses till the day of discharge from the hospital
Apart from this, a health
insurance plan for treatment protects you and your family from the
risks of medical expenses.
This plan strengthens the insurance coverage of an
individual and the entire family by
paying just Rs. 845 per month. The
premium for this health insurance plan is
calculated by considering the death of the member in the year in which the
insurance cover is Rs. 5. The insurance cover in these health insurance plans is Rs. 5. The insurance cover is Rs. 5. The
room rent expenses incurred during hospitalization till the day of hospitalization till the
day of discharge from the hospital is
not covered
Procedures that
require hospitalization for less than 24 hours are covered Hospitalization expenses taken at home and up
to 10% of other problems are covered
Max Bupa Health Insurance
Companies This plan covers you and your
family  You get complete health cover for your family and can also
avail facilities like claim settlement through cashless medical facilities in Islam.
You can buy a health plan for Rs. 299
per month assuming the
death of a young member in the year of war.
Insurance cover of Rs. 5
with the same period of the year. Policies of many health insurance companies
cover hospitalization expenses. There is no
maximum limit on room rent.
Pre-hospitalization and
post-hospitalization expenses are covered till the day of discharge.
You can also get
treatment for both pre-hospitalization and post-hospitalization expenses till the day of discharge. CharHealth
Family Health Insurance
provides family health insurance at a premium. By taking this plan,
you get complete health cover and you do
not have to worry about the medical bills of yourself and your family. By
spending Rs. 973 per month, you
can buy a plan assuming the death of a young member
in the year of war. Insurance cover of Rs. 5
with the same period of the year. CharHealth
Family Health Insurance covers the main hospitalization
expenses like room rent in this policy.
Hospitalization expenses up to four days before hospitalization and the
day after discharge from the hospital are covered in this policy.
Post hospitalization expenses up to 24 hours can be taken at home.
Aditya Birla Group Health Policy
covers healthcare needs of all age groups. This policy
offers comprehensive coverage and
rewards you for maintaining good health.
It also covers chronic diseases like diabetes, hypertension and diabetes.
You can take this policy at Rs 833 per month. The
premium for this health insurance
plan is Rs 5000. Insurance cover for the member was taken at Modern School
with a policy term of one year.
Key features of the health insurance plan: Post hospitalization expenses
like room
rent, operation theatre charges up to
30 days before hospitalization and up to 50
days after discharge from the hospital. ₹500 Subscribe If
hospitalization is required for less than 24 hours,
discharge at
home is subject to the conditions mentioned in the policy. There are
plenty of options for the best family floater health insurance plans in India.
Definitely a good option for your appointee by visiting our video conference. What is
good for one person may
not necessarily be good for the other.
Best family floater health insurance available in India
Some examples of the schemes are
given above. We have given the list of schemes in ascending order from
cheapest to most expensive and
also the details of the benefits of these schemes. We want to
emphasize the need of investing in health insurance scheme so that you can
get the benefits under this Act and friends, this video is
just for example.
Apart from the policies mentioned above, you can
take health insurance policy for yourself and your family.